AADARSH KATIYAR

Rohini, New Delhi | 8299004465 | adarshkatiyar9956@gmail.com

Profile Statement

An adaptable and enthusiastic person having 3.5 years of experience in Sales, Portfolio Management, Relationship Building, Finance & Accounting, MIS maintaining and Operational. Really skilled in handling pressure. I have always focused in diversifying my knowledge which will help me to perform better in your organisation and will be a great resource with some great outcomes.

Experience

HDFC Bank Assistant Manager	2022 – 2023
K.V. Info Services Pvt Ltd. Sales Executive	2018 – 2021
Education	
Jagran College of Arts, Science and Commerce, B.COM	2018 – 2021

Major: Finance & Accounting

Skills & Courses (with Certificates)

- Excel Mastery
- Tally ERP 9 with GST Taxation
- IRDA (Insurance Regulatory and Department)
- NISM (National Institute of Securities and Market, Mutual Funds)
- Digital Marketing
- Google Ads
- BPYBP (Bank Plus Young Bankers Program)

Achievements

- Won 15 Singing Competitions with 7 Certificates and 8 trophies
- Won a **Presentation Competition** (Topic: Role of social media in One's Life)
- 2 Prizes in Treasure Hunt game in college
- 1 Prize in Art Competition
- Recently represented Kanpur (Hometown) in IIT Bombay (Mood Indigo)
- Got an appreciation certificate for opening HDFC securities (HSL accounts)